For generations, Bugatti has been more
than a name. It has been a benchmark. A
benchmark for precision. A benchmark for
craftsmanship. A benchmark for what
should never be compromised. Every
Bugatti is built with belief that
perfection is not optional. It is
required. This is a machine created
under one principle. Nothing, absolutely
nothing should disturb its integrity.
Well, until now. Bugatti,
you don't want to sell me [__] parts,
huh? Bugatti, you don't want to sell me
parts. Okay, no problem. You know, I I
I've been a follower of Bugatti. I've
been a brand representative of Bugatti
for a very long time. I'm always wearing
the hat Bugatti [__] hoodie, but no
longer. All right,
it's [__] war. I'm done being the
good guy. I'm in my winter arc mode. I'm
in my villain arc where I even shave my
head. What [laughter] happened to your
head?
>> Yeah, bro. I was so stressed cuz Bugatti
wasn't cooperating with me selling me
parts for the Bugatti that I lost my
[__] hair. So, you know what? It's
warm. Let me put on another hoodie
because it's uh pretty cold out here.
One second. So, Bugatti, you don't want
to sell me parts. Okay, no problem. Not
a [__] issue. We will get this done
one way or another. So, we have a lot to
talk about in this video. how I bought
my Bugatti bag, how I really crashed,
how Bugatti is basically cornering me
and giving me an ultimatum, and how
parts were stolen off of my Bugatti, and
how I got them back by one simple
message. Oh, and obviously the game plan
with what we're going to do with the
Bugatti since Bugatti no longer wants to
cooperate with us. Shall we begin? All
right, ladies and gentlemen, good
morning. It is currently 9 in the
morning.
>> Someone's excited.
>> I know. I'm pretty excited. We are 56
minutes away from making [__] history
again. from buying [music] technically
my third Bugatti. So, we just lost the
highest bid. We were the last previous
highest bid, but the auction is up in 56
minutes. I just know it cuz I've looked
at this 100,000 times. And right now,
we're here at Cario Motorcars because
Mr. Cario himself said, "Yo, we got to
buy this car back together right now and
we got to do it at the dealer." I'm
like, "All right." So, we're pulling up
and we're going to buy it at the
auction. I'm going to be clicking the
button trying to get the last bid. Our
goal is to buy under a million because
the transaction fee to buy the car from
Copart is 12%. So let's say I buy for 2
million plus 12% it's almost an extra
quarter million dollars which [__]
sucks.
>> All right. What are we doing today?
>> We're buying it.
>> Yo, he's camera shy.
>> We're going to buy it.
>> You got to tell us
>> who's camera shy. We're going to [__]
buy it. That's what we're going to do.
We're going to [__] buy it.
>> Bam.
>> Monster, [laughter]
bro.
>> Look at this. Oh [__] We might win it.
>> Bonus time. The knockoff bit won. THE
KNOCKOFF BIT.
>> [laughter]
>> [__] THAT GUY. [laughter] WELL, who's
going to pay for it now? I'm not paying
for that [__]
>> Can you make me a standard disclaimer
for a video to protect myself in case of
liability and getting sued by a billion
dollar brand? This video is based off of
personal experience and opinions only.
Everything I say is forformational and
entertainment purposes. It is not a
statement nor fact, nor is it meant to
harm, defame, or misrepresent any brand
or company. I'm simply sharing my
perspective, my experience, and viewers
should form their own conclusion based
off of this.
Let's begin, shall we? All right, so
let's first talk about buying back my
Bugatti Chiron, right? So, a lot of
people are like, "Wait, if you own the
car, how do you buy the car back?"
Right? Which I don't even understand how
people don't understand this, but maybe
some people have never gone through
insurance and have done claims in the
past. So I had my pink Bugatti Chiron
and then I had this one. I ended up
trading my pink Bugatti for a plane that
I have. So I have a Lear 45, a light
jet, something just to get around with
the boys and I stayed with this Bugatti.
About 3 weeks later, I crashed this
Bugatti, right? So then once I crashed
[music] this Bugatti, obviously I go
through insurance to go make a claim.
Hey, I got into an accident. Um, you
know, can you guys pay me out of my car?
After back and forth for about 6, seven
months,
it's okay. We finally got paid out on
the Bugatti. Oh, I am no longer the
owner of this car. The bank pays me my
equity and then they give the financing
bank cuz I was financing this car
previously. They give the bank what they
own the car for.
>> You mean renting
>> renting the car for the insurance owns
this car. So, as soon as the insurance
owns this vehicle, they basically could
do whatever they want with it and
usually what they would do is they would
send it to auction. Basically, after
going to auction, it was me bidding and
and one other guy from the UK. I thought
it was Matt Armstrong at start offs, but
he said it wasn't him. So, it was me and
this guy bidding on the auction and then
we bought it back and now it's here. So,
we basically bought it back from the
insurance indirect. We broke the record
on the most expensive vehicle sold in
Copart history. Copart has been around
for like 45 years and the youngest
person ever, 25 years old, has just
bought back the most expensive car in
the [__] history of [__] Copart
history. From this point on, we're going
to intercept and interfere with a lot of
history that's going to happen. We're
going to make new history from this
point forward. We're going to make a lot
of the big boys, old people mad because
the new wave is here. So, broke the
record in Cop Park, right? Moving on
from that, pretending like that's not a
big deal. So, I get the Bugatti, get it
back here, get a couple of my, you know,
my professional mechanics just
go. [laughter]
>> We got it running. You know, I like,
wow, car wasn't running. Bugatti quoted
us uh $1.7 million, almost $2 million to
repair this car. and my Mexican
cameraman fixed it in 30 seconds. Well,
let's pretend like that's not a big
deal. And you know, we'll get into a
little bit further that later into this
video. But when we get this vehicle, I
start posting about it. I'm like, "Hey,
we finally have it back." And I get a
DM. And they're like, "Hey, bro. Just
letting you know I have the bottom
carbon skid plate for a car just like
yours, just in case if you don't have
it."
>> What a coincidence.
>> The [__] What do you mean that I don't
have it? Like, why would you assume that
I don't have the carbon skid plate to
the bottom of my car? Like, at no point
have I done any videos of the bottom of
my car? Why would you assume that I
don't have it? So, I jack up the car.
So, let's jack it up real quick. Let me
show you guys what I did.
>> Yep.
>> Where?
>> Oh. Oh.
>> Oh, [__] Right there.
>> Yep.
>> I don't think he's there either.
>> Oh, [__]
[screaming]
Yep. It's exactly what I thought. Come,
come on in here.
>> So, as you can tell, this down here, if
you can even see it, this is not
supposed to be exposed like this. This
supposed to be like a carbon skid plate,
which basically protects the car and
make sure that it stays planted to the
ground when you're going 250 mph. And I
come down here and I'm like, "Oh,
they're not here. What a coincidence."
Well, sir, can I see a picture of of
what you have to see if it's actually,
you know, fits my view? He's like,
"Yeah, man. Sure. I'll I'll send you a
picture."
>> Send me a picture like this. I'm like,
"Wow, that's exactly what the [__] I
need on my car. What a coincidence. Hey
sir, where did you find this part? Uh,
just out of curiosity because I'm
actually missing that in my vehicle.
He's like, "Oh, bro, I don't know." But
I bought it off some guy off of Facebook
Marketplace and I tried to use it to
build my car and I couldn't. So, I'll
sell it to you if you need it. Like, oh,
okay, sure, but how much do you want for
the carpet ski plate that actually is my
cars? Oh, bro, if you go to Bugatti and
you ask them how much, they'll tell you
$150,000. I'll sell it to you for
$100,000. like, "No, you're going to
sell me my own skid plate that you stole
from my vehicle for 100 grand." All
right. What was your name, sir? His name
was Josh. Like, all right, Josh. You
have 24 hours to give me back my [__]
skid plate, or we're going to open up an
investigation under you and under
wherever this car was taken to in
transport from one shop to another, and
not only are you going to go down, but
the shop that helped you interfere with
taking my part are going to go down.
It's like, bro, what are you talking
about? Like, I have nothing to do with
that. I bought it off of Facebook
Marketplace. I'm like, all right, cool.
So then it has something to do with you.
Send me the listings to the Facebook
marketplace and everything will be okay.
We'll go after that guy. It's like, "Oh,
bro, I forgot my [__] login to my
Facebook Messenger." I'm like, "Dude,
that's [__] cuz you've had this [__]
for like a week." And the [__] idiot
is like, "Bro, thieves are so stupid.
This guy sends me a picture of my own
carbon plate. This is from the accident.
I have a hole in the bottom of my carbon
plate. This is from when I when I
crashed. I ran something over. I told
him, "Look, bro, if you're not going to
give me the parts, it's all good. We're
going to open investigation and we'll
get the parts and we'll get whoever is
involved." no reply for about 5 minutes.
Five minutes later, he sent me a pin of
exactly where he dropped off the part
and he's like, "Hey, bro. The parts are
there. I don't want nothing to do with
this. I don't want to get in trouble.
The parts are there. Everything from
your car." And he pretty much just
blocked my number. I sent two of my guys
over there and they picked up this and
other parts that were missing from the
car. Isn't that [__] crazy? So,
everybody wants to see the up and parts
of the vehicle. So, I'm going to use my
trusty hammer here to kind of work our
way around things just in case if you
can't see them well enough. So, let's
start off with the most obvious, which
is the front end of this vehicle.
This is a bit split up over here. This
is probably the most damaged area right
here.
As you can tell, all of that's pretty
strong, right? Obviously, we have all of
our front end of the vehicle right here,
which is uh pretty much coming off.
Coming on back over here, you have this
hose, which snaps. You have no idea what
this hose is from.
>> That goes straight to the combobulator.
>> The combobulator. Yes. the [__]
[__] combobulator. Our
windshield is cracked. So, our
windshield is broken. We have slightly
damaged or scratched our carbon tub.
>> We keep focusing on the negative. Look
at the positive.
>> Oh, yeah. These This is probably the
most gangster thing Bugatti or should I
say Volkswagen has ever done. We have
carbon fiber windshield wipers. Very
cool. Obviously, the majority of the
damage is done in the front of the
vehicle. Our front splitter
is pretty [__] up. This fender is
messed up. Our headlights, this is
probably the only thing that I I
genuinely care about are these [__]
headlights. Like, look at this. These
headlights are beautiful. The carbon
fiber inside of the headlight, which is
massive. And this right here is just my
favorite part.
>> Do it again.
>> You didn't hear it?
>> I didn't hear it. Do it again for the
people in the back.
>> Did the people in the back hear it?
>> Yeah.
>> Did the people in the front hear it? Did
the people in the in the in the people
in the Bugatti facility hear it? Well,
if they didn't, you [__] are
going to hear now. Stepped on [__]
[__] bro. You stepped on.
Shit's about to get real. Bugatti quoted
me $1.7 million to fix my [__] car.
$1.7 million to fix my car, right? Okay.
All right. $1.7 million. I'm like, well,
that's a lot, right? [__] If I buy the
car back for $1.9 million, $2 million
plus 1.7, that means I would be into the
car about $8.5 million. That's out of my
budget. So they tried to scare me, but
you know what? I'm a trader. I don't get
scared easily. So what do I do? I buy
the car back. I buy the car back. You
know, show a little bit of videos
online, talk about a little bit of [__]
Guess what? Bugatti is blowing up my
phone. I've had multiple meetings with
the CEO of Bugatti. I've had multiple
meetings with the director of Bugatti
America. And they came to me with an
interesting proposal, almost something
that was irresistible, but made me
realize the value of Bugatti and if
these cars should even really be valued
at what they're valued, 5, even $6
million. So the first original quote,
remember it was $1.7 million from
Bugatti itself. I meet with the director
of Bugatti America here in Miami. And he
comes to me. He's said, "Hey, look, man.
We understand what you want to do with
the vehicle. We understand you want to
fix the vehicle. We understand that you
want to get your content out of it. And
there's this guy out there, Matt
Armstrong, that wants to come and fix
the vehicle, but we need to make sure
that we could preserve the brand and
that nobody that is not Bugatti
certified doesn't touch this vehicle.
We've made you an irresistible offer."
Okay, sure. What What What's the offer,
sir? He's like, "Okay, well, you could
come and fix your vehicle directly with
us in France. We'll pay for the
shipping." So, Bugatti will pay for the
$40, $50,000 shipping to France and back
to America, and we can repair your whole
entire vehicle, including carbon tub,
including a new transmission, new front
end, new interior, new airbags,
basically a brand new Bugatti, and it
will be stamped by Bugatti, certified,
rebuilt by Bugatti. I'm like, "Fuck, how
much is that going to cost?" How much
you think they said? It's probably like
>> I don't know. I'm I'm going to say a
humble amount. 3 mil,
>> right? You would assume a very high
amount if they're going to give me a
brand new carbon tub. They're going to
give me a brand new transmission.
They're going to strip the car down to
the bone. Literally remove everything.
Like leave it on the carbon tub like
this picture right here, like naked. I
wouldn't even be able to recognize the
car. They told me $600,000 and 6 months
and we'll do all of that to your
vehicle. Just please do not touch the
vehicle. Do not have anybody else repair
it. only have Bugatti technicians touch
it, we will do this offer for you." I'm
like, "Fuck." Considering the fact that
they came down 70% from their original
$1.7 million offer for just parts and
minor labor, now they're basically
dropping the engine, splitting the car
in half cuz the carbon tub connects. And
they're doing all of that for 600 grand
and a new tub and a new transmission.
[__] That that sounds like a good deal,
right? And as I'm further thinking about
it, I'm like, why would they knock down
70% of their original quote? Are their
margins that high? Why can they go from
$1.7 million to $600,000 over one
conversation? What you pay for this car
is hype. Is pure sheer hype. There's
nothing special about this car other
than it has a W16 engine in the back.
You put a [__] W16 engine in a Toyota
Corolla, you're going to go 200 mph. No
[__] [__] The problem with Bugatti
is that they don't want the value of
their brand to go down. They don't want
somebody like me, somebody like Matt
Armstrong to come and touch on this car
because if so, one of us can do it in a
backyard, what would that do to their
brand? That would devalue their brand.
Think about it. This is a billion dollar
company, right? This billion dollar
[__] company has now just knocked off
70% of the value of their parts to get
me through the door. Why? Cuz they want
to hold me by the balls. They want me to
ship the car to France. And as soon as I
ship the car to France, I no longer have
possession of the vehicle. And guess
what? They're going to want to take a
year, two years to rebuild my car. And
then guess what? I'm not going to let
that happen. I'm not going to lose
possession of my car. A brand that just
knocked off 70% of their value. They
literally just put their pants down and
said, "We need you to come bring us a
car. If not, the value of our vehicles
are going to go down." Well, guess what?
>> I woke up.
[music]
>> And honestly, I never expected in my 25
years of life that I would have a
relationship or even have the phone
number of the CEO of Bugatti. And I
would never expect for the CEO of
Bugatti to switch up on me. Let me give
you guys a little bit of context, right?
So, ever since the whole accident
happened, Matt Rimac has been very fast
to respond. I literally posted on
Instagram. I said, "Yo, this Bugatti,
you have 24 hours to reply if I'm going
to get parts for this car or not, or I
will 3D [__] print parts for this
car. I don't give a [__] right? Cuz I
need to fix my car somehow." And he
responded within like 18 hours. I'm
like, "Holy shit." The power of social
media. Okay, cool. I speak to Matt Rimac
back and forth through the DMs. I get
his number. I got on the phone with him
and Matt tells me, "Hey, look, first of
all, I don't appreciate the fact that
you guys are saying that the car is
blacklisted. The car has never been
blacklisted in its existence. Bugatti
wouldn't do that to its customers or its
cars. So, please clear up that
narrative." Okay, cool. I'll clear that
up right now. The car was never
blacklisted. So, Matt Rimck told me that
he could get me the headlights for about
$40 to $50,000. I'm like, "Amazing.
[__] How can we like how can we get
them? Where do we start?" He's like,
"Look, let's have a second conversation.
we just want to make sure that we can
work together in this, but I give you my
word that I will get you parts for that
car and we're going to work together on
this. I'm like, "Okay, cool. So, you're
going to help us get parts. We're going
to work together in this." He's like,
"Yeah, if I have to get one of the
Bugatti certified mechanics and
technicians out there to make sure that
it's being rebuilt properly, I will do
that. I got you." All right, cool. So,
proceeds to taking two three days to
having a meeting with the rest of his
team and one of the Bugatti
representatives of America comes out and
basically gives us the proposal that I
have just mentioned to you guys. And I
speak again with Matt. I'm like, "Hey,
Matt. So, is there any possible event or
any scenario where you're going to
actually sell us parts?" He's like, "No,
absolutely not. Parts will not be sold
to you unless the car gets sent to
friends and then we repair it there."
So, basically, long story short, he hit
us with the Uno reverse and we're not
getting headlights. We're not getting
[__] And what really gets me is that I
I'm very strong on my word. When I get
my word that I'm going to do something,
I'm going to do it. Period. No matter
what. He gave me his word that he was
going to support and help us throughout
this journey no matter what to make sure
that we protect the brand and we can get
this car taken care of, right? Who wants
to have a crash Bugatti? Nobody. And he
hit us with the Uno reverse card. I'm
like, [__] So, honestly, Matt Remac, I
really wish we could have worked
together on this vehicle. Looks like
we're going to have to leave that for
another project in the future. And all I
can say is set and forget. And we're
going to have to turn on the 3D [__]
printer. Have to. Now, I've already had
an interesting experience with Bugatti
earlier this year. So when I had this
Bugatti before it was crashed and I had
my pink Bugatti. I had two Bugattis at
the time. Honestly, I felt like the king
of the [__] world. So guess what I
wanted? I wanted a third Bugatti. So I
heard that there was this gentleman
named Evan at Miller Motors, which is
the top sales for Bugatti in America.
And he had this Bugatti Mistro and that
the person that had [music] purchased it
was giving up his allocation. And the
only way for you to actually buy this
mistro off of this person that no longer
wants the allocation is you have to pay
over Sticker. And if you pay over
sticker, you wave the whole preferred
client of Bugatti, right? Because for
you to buy a client of Bugatti, you have
to be a preferred client. So if you pay
over sticker, you kind of wave all that
and anybody can buy the car as long as
they pay 800K over sticker. I'm like,
[__] okay, whatever. I get on the phone
with Evan and I'm like, hey, look, you
know, can we work something out with
800k over sticker? Can I pay a little
bit less? Like, can we work something
out? He's like, no, anybody can buy this
car. He's like, yo, by paying this 800k
over sticker, you basically are now a
preferred client by Bugatti. We can get
any allocation from this point forward.
I'm like, [__] I might have to bite the
bullet on this first one. Be the
youngest 25-year-old to have three
Bugattis. First one to have a mistro.
And now I can pretty much get into the
door. I can get a turbion and whatever's
to come in the future, right? Because I
am only 25. I plan to have more Bugattis
in the future. Okay, cool. You know
what, Evan? [__] it. Let's do it. Bill,
Bill, 800K over sticker. I'll buy the
Mistro. [__] it. We'll figure out how we
get this relationship with Bugatti built
later. Okay, cool. I sent Evan all of my
information. Send him my Instagram cuz
he wants to see who I am, right? because
right he wants to make sure who's he's
selling [music] the car to. He's like,
"Who's this 25-year-old that's buying a
third Bugatti and is paying 800k over
sticker?" Evan proceeds to call me back
about 30 minutes later. He's like,
"Look, man. Uh yeah, I just want to let
you know I don't really think that this
car is the right fit for you." Like,
"What do you mean?" Like, "Yeah, I just
don't think this car represents you
right now. I I think it makes sense for
you just to wait a little bit. Maybe you
can find a different Bugatti." Like, I I
don't understand. The whole point is
anybody can buy this Bugatti. It's a
right fit for anybody as long as they
pay the 800k over sticker. And he's
like, "Yeah, no. It just it just won't
work, man. Have a nice day. Hangs up the
phone. What the [__]
>> Got you, [__]
>> So, I couldn't even buy a third Bugatti,
even if I'm paying 800k over sticker. At
this point, I don't understand. And if
it's because I'm 25, is it because I
have a pink and purple Bugatti? Is it
because I'm Cuban? This whole criteria
was pretty interesting to me at that
time. And I I don't get it, See the
cars. Why would they not want to sell me
a third Bugatti? I don't understand.
>> Yeah. It's not like we abuse them. It's
not like we dress them. It's not like
they red light them. I I don't get it,
bro.
>> Not like we forget basic maintenance,
>> brother. We don't drift them. We don't
drive them. We don't stand on them. We
don't do anything. We just take
pictures, right?
>> Yeah. I mean, we always have wipers.
That's what I'm saying. But I know a guy
that could actually repair this vehicle
cuz uh my Mexican cameraman over here
might not be the best guy.
>> I think we're going to need to phone a
friend.
>> Phone a friend. Let's phone a friend.
There's this guy named Matt Armstrong.
Have you guys heard of him? Probably.
Right. So, he supposedly fixed cars. He
supposedly wanted to fix this car, but
let's call him now to see if he really
[music] wants to fix it.
>> What's up? Oh,
>> what's up, mate?
>> Oh, good. How are you?
>> Hey, where you at, mate? [laughter]
>> We're in sunny England, of course. It's
really nice and sunny.
>> Yeah, I mean, Miami is not that good as
well, but I I think I got something that
you might like, bro. The Bugatti.
>> Oh my days. The Bugatti. [laughter]
>> Yo, so look, so look, I'm not going to
lie, right? I I'm not a trained
professional, right? All I know is that
like this windshield is no longer good,
right? So, we can just like
[laughter]
Oh my god.
>> Wait, the windshield's no longer good,
right? So, we can just [laughter]
>> You know how much You know how much that
is?
>> How much is it? [laughter]
>> It's at least like $15,000.
>> What?
>> That's actually pretty cheap.
>> Not [__] mad. All right, look. All
right, look. [laughter]
>> Keep smashing it.
>> All right, look. So, there's there's
this [__] right here, right? I'm not a
professional, but all I know is that you
got to like get it out of there, right?
You got to get it out of there, right?
[__]
>> This is fine.
>> Stop. [laughter]
>> Well, and then this right here. I know.
I I know we got to fix this right here.
We got like no
>> no. All right. [laughter]
>> No.
>> All right, mate. Well, obviously I don't
know how to fix this car. You think you
could come down and fix it? [laughter]
>> I I I think I think we can come out and
fix it. It's going to cost It's going to
be expensive, [laughter] but it might be
cheaper than Bugatta.
>> Yeah, I'm not going to lie. Even if even
if yours is more expensive than Bugatti,
I'd rather pay you than pay Bugatti all
day, bro. I'm not even going to lie,
bro. For real.
>> Yeah, I think it's quite snotty the part
situation and everything. And yeah, I I
don't necessarily agree with it either,
but if we can do it without them, then
um yeah, I think we we've proven a
point. We can prove a point. But let's
see. Let's see. Let's see if it is even
possible.
>> How long do you think it'll take for you
to rebuild this car? making the parts or
what? [laughter]
>> Um, getting the parts. We We'll get them
somehow.
>> If If we had the parts, if they had the
parts, we could build that car in a
week.
>> In a week.
>> In a week, we'd be we we'll be able to
build that car. If we had the parts, but
that could be an issue. [laughter]
>> Okay. So, I'm going to So, this this is
my game plan here, right? So, this is
what I'm going to do. I'm going to I'm
going to put a tent right here, and then
we're going to fix it right right here.
Is that Does that work for you?
>> I'm down for that. I'm down for that.
That'd be sick.
>> Yeah. So, that works for you, right? If
we put a tent right here and we just fix
it right here.
>> Yeah. We're going to do it like proper
like Indian style [laughter] like
>> we're going to flip the flipflops out
on.
>> No, I I mean, when do you think you
could come down to Miami and take a look
at it?
>> So, let's We're going to come down just
after Christmas so I don't get in
trouble with the misses and we'll be
that week there. We'll come down. We'll
strip all the broken parts off, work out
what we can get, what we can fix, what
we can't get, and then we can go from
there. At least that that sounds like
the best option for us. So we So we at
least got like a base of where we can go
get all the bad stuff off it and then we
know what we need to replace.
>> Okay. Should we start removing any parts
for you? Would you want us to do
anything any work? [laughter]
>> No. Keep driving it. Keep making videos.
>> Just don't break it anymore.
>> You you sure we we could like we could
drop the transmission for you if you
want. Right. Like I I I I'll figure it
out. No,
>> no. [laughter]
>> All right. Sick. All right. So, I I'll
see you last week of December here in
Miami.
>> Yeah, I'm ready. I'm ready for it.
>> Okay. Sick. All right. Well, Matt, safe
travels when you come down here and I'll
see you soon.
>> See you then. Bye. Bye. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> How about that, Bugatti? Huh? We got
Matt [__] Armstrong going to
come fix the car. Now, what? Huh? I'm
taking this [__] personal, bro. I I
relax.
We actually need this. [laughter]
Like when do you ever just get the
chance to get a hammer and just throw it
on Bugatti? Like just tell me when do
you ever get the chance to do that?
Never. Right. Well, you're not [__]
rich enough. [__] you. I really broke
the windshield, bro.
So, look. I mean, this airbag might be
Volkswagen, but just to show you how
good Volkswagen builds this car, the
horn works. Look at this.
>> There's less things we got to fix. Well,
right. We have the air. The horn works,
so we don't really need the airbag. If
you think about it, brother, if you get
me a knife right now, I can cut this out
right here. We will sew this back up cuz
this is very easily sewed back on. And
that's it. You have a car that has a
horn. I mean, the inside of the car is
fine. We did break the the sky view. So,
as you guys can tell, we did break this
sky view, which I don't even know how
this cracked. I guess like on impact, it
had a slight crack and over time it just
broke. Uh, obviously the floor airbags
have been completely bloated. Very dirty
cuz, you know, we have been driving the
vehicle up and down a couple of times.
The [__] went here? Oh, look. They stole
these parts as well.
This [__] [__]
>> So, obviously the back of the vehicle is
perfectly fine. Nothing really happened
back here. The wing
still indestructible. We'll give that to
Bugatti. This is a great wing. Moving on
to this. I bringing the car in through
this fence over here. I uh curb rashed
it pretty [__] bad. So, funny story.
As soon as I got this car, I didn't like
the bronze wheels. So, we plastic dipped
these wheels. I'm talking about like the
same hour that I got this car. This is
not going to surface the internet until
probably like a year from now. So,
>> you know what's amazing? I am probably
the first and only person on the planet
and YouTube to do this.
Bugatti is probably looking at this
like, "What the [__] is going on?" As I
was doing it, I'm like, I think I've
reached that level of rich where I just
don't even give a [__] Fact that I'm
plastic dipping the wheels of a car that
people don't even get to see in their
life. And the people that do get to
afford it don't even drive is just the
biggest [__] you. And to kind of finish
off the Bugatti beef just for this video
alone, because we're really only getting
started, what they've done to me is deny
me an opportunity, unless it's under
their dictatorship, which is very
unpatriotic, considering that most of
their customers are actually in North
America and this is the land of the
free. And most of their customers could
agree because they're built on free
spirit and being more of a leader than a
follower. So, [music] I don't think it's
fair the way they've treated their
youngest customer. And I think the one
of the most that could represent [music]
them in the best way possible. And now
what we're going to do is tell and show
the people the reality behind this
amazing brand. It could really be a
backyard Bugatti build. BBB, just how
you like. [laughter]
>> What is that even supposed to stand for?
>> Big Bad Boats. [laughter]
All right, so I'm going to see if the
car turns on. So, I never got access to
the real key as you guys saw before. So,
this is my current key. I tore it up a
little bit just because I got mad at it
and I even I even broke the
the [snorts] speed key on it. Totally
kidding. This is the real key. Bugatti,
you have some [__] explaining to me.
Why does your key your $25,000 key to a
$5 million car look identical to a
[__] Chevy key?
Let's turn this [__] on.
>> Oh, bro, she has no gas.
>> Probably buzzing on the last
>> [__] All right, let's push this out.
Oh, I have Oh, we should get the we
should get the the tow truck and the
forklift to get it out.
>> For this type of transport, they
probably charge I don't know how much.
10 grand to transport. This is how I
transport my back.
You're good. You're good. You're good.
Yep. That look that looks good enough.
All right. Looks like we're doing good.
>> Oh, come on. Not the [__] tow truck,
bro. Come on. Come on. Oh. Oh.
Oh my god.
>> Hey, that sounds so crunchy.
That's how you tow truck your Bugatti
out of your basketball court.
>> All right, so figured
it would be a smarter idea to go get gas
instead of pulling it out with the toll
car. So, let's go get gas real quick. By
the way, nobody's really seen this car
on YouTube yet. Everybody's seen the
short form degeneracy we've done with
it, but let's welcome let's give a warm
welcome to the famous M3.
>> Brother,
>> oh my god, I've been watching your
videos for the past [__] sake. Do you
mind stopping real quick, bro? Please.
Please. You have no idea.
>> Okay.
>> My My son's going to freak out.
>> Let's go to the gas station.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> What's up? What's going on?
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
>> Who's that?
>> Yo. Yo.
>> Who the [__] is
>> [__] Freddy's good. Oh my god.
>> What was I doing last night? What was I
doing last night?
>> Bro, bro, Alex, my dad was watching your
whole 10our video, bro. I've been trying
to figure out.
>> Yo, we were just talking about you right
now again. Yo, nice to meet you,
brother. Nice to meet you,
>> bro. I I'm I'm I'm trying to do the same
thing you are doing, brother. Brother,
I'm still I'm still looking at your
videos. I'm just [__] going crazy
that you're literally I'm literally
standing next to you right now.
>> Look, I I SHAVED MY HEAD.
>> OH [__]
>> WHAT MADE you do it? I just did it.
>> Oh, he wants to ask you a [__]
question.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Look, I shaved my head.
>> Look.
>> Holy [__] Yo, the cut is fire.
>> I know. What's up,
>> bro? Bro, look. Look.
>> I've been on a losing streak recently
and I need some words of like
encouragement, bro. I just lost like two
trades. You know, I'm learning off of
one of the people that learned off you
and he's like teaching me and [__] What
are some inspirational words you can
give me to help me keep going?
>> Set and forget, bro. That's all I got to
say. [laughter]
>> Losing streaks are part of the process,
bro. It's normal. Just, you know, just
keep going at it. Stick to your risk
management. Stick to the strategy and
and set and forget, bro. Losing streaks
are part of the process.
>> You got to keep going and then that's
how you get out of it.
>> Thank you, bro. Thank you, bro.
>> All right. Good luck, brother. See you,
man.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Likewise. Hey,
>> love you, brother. Thank you, man. Hey,
I love the whip, bro.
>> That's That's insane, dude.
>> Honestly, respectfully, if you own a
Bugatti and you can't put your Bugatti
in your backyard, you're not rich
enough. Respectfully, if you can't put
your Bugatti next to your pool inside of
your basketball court, you're not
[__] rich enough. Save the guy
carrying a [__] fuel tank. Yo, we got
to make sure that this is the fuel side.
Yes.
Big mistake. The other side looks
exactly the same. When you open it up,
it's the oil. So you could very and look
and it opens up very easily as well.
It's not like it's difficult. You know,
obviously you would take this out. If
you're a [__] idiot, you would put it
in. How do I know it's going?
>> Yeah. Now it's going.
>> So more of the story, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> So Evan, go [__] yourself. Because if I
would have probably got my third
Bugatti, if I would have gotten my
Mistro, this would have probably never
happened, you [__] So this is
probably why you are no longer the top
sales for Bugatti in America. That's why
Abraham from Lamborghini Broward is the
top sales for Bugatti in America because
he actually cares about his customers
and creates a long-term relationship
with them. So, shout out to the guys at
Lamborghini Broward. Shout out to the
guys in Carrier Motorc Cars because
without them, they would not facilitate
this experience of buying these Bugattis
and not having this strict agenda that a
certain type of person has to buy these
cars. Hey man, if you're successful, if
you like cars and you can afford it, you
should be able to [__] buy them. The
guys at Lamborghini Broward, I know we
had a little uh miscommunication with
the parts of this vehicle and that they
went missing. That was my bad. I
apologize for that. There's a
miscommunication from my sources. My
sources were unreliable at that moment
and just want to clear those things up.
So, yes, everything with the car is
good. So, you know, right now I want to
recreate cuz I want you guys to
understand, right? I know a lot of you
guys love me and a lot of you guys were
really scared for the fact that I got
into the accident with this Bugatti. So,
right now, I want to recreate this
accident and how it happened. So, let's
get get in here. Get in here. Close.
Close.
All right. All right. So, this is
exactly how this accident happened,
right? So, let me kind of hide the
airbag a little bit. Kind of put that in
there. So, this happened after UFC fight
in Miami. So, I had just met Donald
Trump. I had just pretty much just been
right next to him shaking his hand. I
left there like the [__] man, bro. I
just met Trump. I'm getting escorted out
through the VIP section of UFC. I'm the
first guy out. They have my police
escort in front. I get in my Bugatti.
They escort me out of the arena and then
I'm pretty much just alone there going
home. Bro, I feel like the man. I'm not
going to lie. Right. 24, 25 years old,
just met Trump, getting escorted out of
the UFC. I think I made money on that
fight. I think I made like 23,000 on the
fight. I'm going home like the man. So,
as soon as the police escort left, I'm
like, "Okay, cool. It's perfect. It's
time." I pull out my phone. I start
texting and driving. After I'm texting
and driving, I'm closing out a position
on Euro USD at $35.7 million that I'm
closing out [music] on one of these
positions. And as I'm closing out one of
these positions, I open up a memecoin.
And on this meme coin, I look up and I'm
at a red light. So, I continue to trade.
That's not how it happened. So obviously
that is a joke. That is not how it
happens. You should never text and
drive. I was not texting and driving.
You should never trade and drive.
>> No tea and drive. No texting and
driving. No trading and driving. Period.
Even if you're in a [__] Bugatti. So
I'm on the highway and as soon as I am
on the far left lane because that's
usually like the faster lane. That lane
is actually going the slowest. So I
decide to merge my way to the right.
There's three lanes. As soon as I go
through the right, there is a 1987
Suzuki mini truck on the far right lane
in front of a bus and I just simply
couldn't see it because there was a
blind spot. It was dark at that area on
the highway. So, as as I'm changing
lanes to the right, uh he's over there
in that far right lane. Obviously, I I
don't see him. So, I just hit him. I
think he might have been going 30 m
hour, 35 mph. Those Suzuki mini trucks
aren't fast at all. I'm going the speed
limit and I just hit him from the back.
It is what it is, right? So then as soon
as I hit him, I literally the airbag is
like in my face. So like this [__]
literally just like
>> So Sea's head actually hit the
windshield right here.
>> Thank god I have a big head. [laughter]
>> Totally kidding. So like as soon as I
crash, boom, the [__] hits my face and
I'm like, whoa. I was for a solid 5
seconds like what the [__] just
happened? And when I look forward, I see
like that the hood is over the the
windshield. And I'm like, there's no
[__] [music] way I just crashed my
Bugatti. And I look down and then these
airbags are on my feet and I'm like,
"Oh, this [__] just really happened." So
I open up the door. When I open up the
door, I see the car that I crashed to. I
like as soon as I hit him, he basically
like moved to the left. So I go help
this person get out [music] the car.
When I help this person get out the car,
he's like sideways in the car like cuz I
guess [music] he wasn't wearing a seat
belt or something. I don't know. He was
like, he was not in his driving
position. And when I hub him out of the
car, he gets out. He's like, "Who was
driving that [__] car? That
[__] Who was driving that car?"
And I'm like, "Sir, sir, [music] sir, it
it was me." And he looks at me and he
goes, "Alex G." Like, "No [__]
[laughter] way, bro." The the irony is
the ratio of both these vehicles on the
road. It's probably like the most
expensive car on the road and the most
inexpensive car on the road. You have a
$3,000 mini truck with a $5 million
hypercar. Like, tell me the [__]
ratio of this accident. Like it could
not be more ironic. So after I chop it
up with him like, "Yo, are you good?
Like I can get you another truck, bro."
Like you know, I see these trucks on
Facebook Marketplace all the time. He's
like, "No, bro. You're good, dude. I've
seen your stuff before. Like, I'm fine."
He walked off perfectly fine. Everything
is good. Everything's chilling. We chat
back and forth. I got his number. We
went out to dinner the next day. I I go
out with his friend. I take my friend.
Like we we almost had a relationship
after that point because honestly,
that's pretty impactful, right? Not
every day do you crash a Bugatti and not
every day do you get crashed by a
Bugatti. About 2 months ago, I get this
letter from my attorney, and he goes,
"Hey, man. Just letting you know,
Jonathan is suing you. So, right now,
we're in a legal battle right now with
the person that I crash into. It's
totally not fair that you walked off the
scene. You're perfectly fine. And I
offer you to get you a new vehicle. You
deny that. And 7 months later, you come
up with this [__] claim that now
you're in pain." Obviously, he's seen
that as a major opportunity. Not every
day are you going to get crashed by a
Bugatti. Somebody else in that position
in that same moment would have probably
like cracked their head against the
[__] like pillar. They would have
like hit it on purpose or something. Who
knows if somebody would have done in
that scenario. I get it. Maybe he needs
the money, but I just don't think that's
the way to go. And asking for an absurd
amount of $750,000 is [__] [__]
It's definitely not going to get that. I
have very good attorneys. Shout out
Hayden Worster because without Hayden
Worster, I would have probably not even
gotten paid out on this car. He
literally helped me get paid out [music]
on this Bugatti. fighting with insurance
every single day, endless hours, working
on weekends, early mornings, late like
he is the person that made sure I got
paid on this car. Hayden Worster, Hayden
Law, whatever it is, if you guys I mean
this is not even a paid promo. I asked
him, I'm like, "Yo, look, bro. Like,
thank you for all the work that you did
genuinely. Like, I really do appreciate
the effortless time that you put into
this. How can I repay?" He's like,
"Brother, nothing, man. I just love
doing cool [__] for cool people." Like,
bro, I [__] with that. You know, I can
have a lot of morals to this story. you
know how the real ones turned on you
when things get hard, how people
crumble, supporters, non-suporters. But
I would really want to take the moral of
this story towards when you get into an
uncomfortable situation like this one,
like crashing a very expensive car and
being held at major liability. You know,
I could have cried myself to sleep every
single night. I could have crumbled. I
could have filed for bankruptcy. I could
have done so many things. But what did I
do? I simply brushed it off. Kept
walking forward with a smile on my face.
No. being put in an uncomfortable
situation is because you can handle it
and you can get out of it. And a lot of
people don't know how to do that. So, I
feel like anybody else in my position
would have crumbled and would have
[__] up this like fumbled this whole
entire thing and I've been able to hold
their composure throughout the whole
thing. I'm just smiling, learning,
laughing throughout the whole entire way
and making great experiences through it.
And that's what I would say is the moral
of the story. You know, accidents
happens. It was my [__] I was held
responsible for it. I'm getting the
shitty end of the stick. I'm losing
money on it. But you know what? I'm
living. I'm learning. And I'm having fun
because, you know, [__] happens. I'm
being held accountable for it. And now
we just got to make the most out of it.
And buying a Bugatti is almost like the
highest point. Like what comes after
buying a Bugatti? Pretty much nothing. I
had two of them. Nobody can top buying
two of them. If you do, it pretty much
makes no [__] sense. And somebody
that would have crashed their Bugatti,
they would have probably just thrown in
the towel. They like, "You know what?
[__] it. This is not for me. This is too
much. [__] it." I turned a negative into
a positive. I turned crashing into a
Bugatti, the most viral thing that I
have ever done. I pushed Jake Paul into
his pre-pressor in a crash Bugatti. I'm
pissing off global [music]
billion-dollar companies at 25 years old
from my basketball court in my backyard.
I have a more viral Bugatti than Andrew
Tate right now. And I'm turning this
positive into a negative so aggressively
that I'm pissing off every single day
people. People are like, "Oh, this guy
doesn't appreciate materialistic things.
It's coming for him." Yeah, bro. I don't
give a [__] about materialistic things.
Like, it doesn't [__] matter. This is
a car. This is replaceable. What is not
replaceable is our lives, is our health,
is our well-being. That is where the
value is at. I'm just having fun with
this materialistic [__] while I have it
right now. Because I'm sure in 5 years
I'm going to get tired of cars and I'm
going to want mega yachts and I'm going
to go have fun with mega yachts. So, I'm
pissing off every regular day, people.
Because yes, I don't give a [__] about a
car like this. And yes, you might work
very hard to get a car like this exactly
how I did. But now, what I want to do
with it is whatever the [__] I want to
do with it. Our values for materialistic
things are very much different. I don't
give a [__] and you do. I remember
working so hard at Dunkin Donuts to
being able to save up to get my trading
account and scaling that trading account
so aggressively and so I can afford my
first supercar, which was my Audi R8.
And as soon as I bought the car, I
didn't give a [__] about it anymore
because what I enjoyed was the journey
to buy the car. Was the ups and downs,
was the battles, was me becoming a
better and stronger person. Having the
car doesn't make me who I am. It's
almost just like that is the result of
what I did. What I did makes me who I
am. If the car is crashed, it's
scratched up, I don't give a [__]
That's just a trophy. Trophy doesn't
mean anything without the battle that
you went through to getting it. So, with
that being said, set and forget. [music]